Guide to the Artists Space Archive MSS.291
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1973 - 2009
  - Margia Kramer: "Part I: Secret" (Installation), January 5, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Patricia Caire: "Black and Light Passages", January 5, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Seth Laderman: Photographic, January 5, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Ann Wilson (with Carol Ligon): Objects for "Gymnast", January 26, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Earl Ripling: Installation, January 26, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Anthony McCall, Pajakowska, Tyndall, Weinstock, Oblowitz, DeLanda, February 16. 1980 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Allan McCollum: Paintings, February 23, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Jeff Balsmeyer: "Giving Peasants Agricultural Advice", February 23, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Jenny Snider: "Painted Drawings, February 23, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Richard Prince: "An Untitled Piece", February 23, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Silvia Kolbowski: "What Was the Right Answer", February 23, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - 7 Toronto Artists: Susan Britton, David Buchan, Paul Campbell, Robin Collyer, Jerry McGrath, John Scott, Shirley Wiitasalo [1 of 2], April 5, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Bruno Bussman: "I Want to Know", April 5, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Guy De Cointet: "Tell Me", April 5, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Ed Levine: "Room Construction", May 17, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "Pool": Documentation of Independently Organized Artists' Installations at CW Post College, May 17, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Reese Williams: An Untitled Work, May 17, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Performance: Stuart Sherman, Fernanda Doty, John Malpede, June 24, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Remembrance for Tomorrow: Sherrie Levine, Richard Prince, Cindy Sherman, Laurie Simmons [New 57 Gallery - Edinburg, Scotland], July 5, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Donald Baechler, Arch Connelly, Nancy Dwyer, James Goss, James Holl, Tom Koken, September 20, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - The Artists and Models Ball: A Benefit Party for Artists Space Sponsored by Chelsea Art Week - Pamphlets, October 25 - 31, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - A Sound Selection: Audio Works by Artists, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Joel Hubaut: "Une Idee en L'air" [1 of 3], October 28, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Joel Hubaut: "Une Idee en L'air" [2 of 3], October 28, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Photographic Work By: David Kulik, Frank Majore, Kevin Noble, Ken Pelka, Pat Place, Rene Santos, Brian Weil, November 1, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Architecture: Sequences - Philippe Guerrier, Jenny Lowe, Lorna McNeur, Deborah Oliver, Peter Wilson, January 17, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Architecture: Sequences - Condition Reports, Loan Forms, Travel, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Myrel Chernick, Carroll Dunham, Tom Rubnitz, January 17, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - "Slides - Music": Peter Grass, Robert Smith, Christof Kohlafer, Nan Goldin, Charlie A. & Fred, Jack Smith, March 4, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Selections from The Unaffiliated Artists File, March 14, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - "It's Just Art": Performance by Adrian Piper, April 28, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Gary Falk, Brigid Kennedy, Ladd Kessler, Peggy Yunque, May 9, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Emergency: 13 Films, June 24, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Philippe Demontaut, Annette Messager, Tom Wolf, September 19, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Sonya Rapoport: "Phase Three of Shared Dynamic Participant Performance", October 15, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Glenys Johnson "Wall Drawing", Meridel Rubenstein "The Lowriders", October 24, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Group Exhibition: Ellen Cooper, Jane Dickson, Bobby G., Rebecca Howland, Cara Perlman, Kiki Smith, Seton Smith, October 24, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 35 Artists Return to Artist Space: A Benefit Exhibition, December 4, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 35 Artists Benefit: Loan Forms, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 35 Benefit Artists: Photographic Materials, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 35 Artists Return: Cindy Sherman Photos, 1979 (Box 10a, Folder 1)
  - 35 Artists Return: Photographs, 1981 (Box 10a, Folder 2)
  - Eating Friends: Jenny Holzer and Peter Nadin, January 9, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Jim Iserman "Patio Tempo", Jim Sanborn "Invisible Forces", January 9, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - No More Magic: Hudson-Buzz Tone Outlet, January 9, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - A Likely Story: Gretchen Bender, David Cabrera, Ronald Jones, Jeff Koons, David Robinson, February 20, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Projects: After All (for RPW) by Stephen Lapthisophon and Stephen Miller Installation, February 20, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Evening Series of Readings and Films, April 1, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Young Fluxus: Carla Liss, April 10, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Young Fluxus: Checklist and Traveling Exhibition Packet, April 10, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Young Fluxus: Correspondence, Loans, April 10, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Young Fluxus: Don Boyd, April 10, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Young Fluxus: Endre Tot, April 10, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Young Fluxus: Essays, April 10, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Young Fluxus: Essays, April 10, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Young Fluxus: Essays, April 10, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Young Fluxus: JH Kocman, April 10, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Young Fluxus: John M. Armleader, April 10, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Young Fluxus: Peter Van Riper, April 10, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Young Fluxus: Photographic Materials, April 10, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Young Fluxus: Rimma and Valery Gerlouin, April 10, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Young Fluxus: Yoshimasa Wada, April 10, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Projects: "Lost Dance Steps" by Bruce Charlesworth, "Rock" by Tad Savinar, April 10, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Richard Baim, Robert Attanasio, Keith Sanborn, May 20, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Paul McMahon, May 22, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Facades, Landscapes, Interiors, May 29, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Group Material: Primer (for Raymond Williams), May 29, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Room 205: Michael Byron "For the Nun", May 29, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Selections from the Unaffiliated Artists File, September 25, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Selections from the Unaffiliated Artists File: Catalogue Text, September 25, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Selections from the Unaffiliated Artists File: Installation Photographic Materials, September 25, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Installations by Redd Ekks, Ken Lum, and Barbara Noah, November 6, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - U.S. Projects: Nic Nicosla - Photographs [Room 205], Peter Waite - "Las Meninas" [Room 207], November 6, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - "Advocate": A Performance by Eric Bogosian, December 8, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Installations by Jurgen Partenheimer and Stewart Wilson, December 11, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Projects: Peter Shelton "Whitehead", December 11, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Victor Alzamora, Jennifer Bolande, Theresa Hak Kyung Cha, Stephen Pollack, December 11, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Dark Rooms: Richard Baim, Dorit Cypis, Perry Hoberman, Antonio Muntadas, Michael Sauer, January 22, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Grand Galop and U.S. Projects: Howard Fried, February 26, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Films: Doug Eisenstark, Leslie Thorton, Dan Walworth, Susan Kouguell, Ernest Marrero, Kristin Lovejoy, Jean-Marie Straub, Daniele Huillet, April 5, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Installation: Paul Hunter, Jonathan Kessler, Kevin Labadie, Tim Maul, Fred Szymanski, Stephen Whisler, April 9, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Gioia Timpanelli: Italian Traveling, A Mantel with Boxes [Room 205], May 14, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles/New York Exchange, May 21, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Los Angeles/New York Exchange: Budget and Correspondence, May 21, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles/New York Exchange: Catalogue Text and Images, May 21, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles/New York Exchange: L.A. Artists, May 21, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles/New York Exchange: NY Artists, May 21, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Artists from the Studio in a School, July 9, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Selections from the Unaffiliated Artists File, October 1, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Ernest Benkert: Meshes, Crosses, Bars, November 5, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - International Projects: Canada, The Architecture of Privacy - Andy Patton, November 5, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - "Hundreds of Drawings": A Benefit Exhibition and Sale for Artists Space, December 10, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - New Galleries of the Lower East Side: Promotional Drafts with Images, January 21, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - New Galleries of the Lower East Side: Loan Forms, January 21, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - International Projects: Belgium and Holland, January 21, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Reconstruction Project: A Benefit Exhibition, January 21, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 3 Artists Select 3 Artists: Lary Johnson Selected by Richard Prince, Annette Lemieux Selected by David Salle, Jolie Stahl Selected by Rebecca Howland, February 25, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Sally Hazelet Drymmond: Paintings, 1971-1984, February 25, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - An Evening of Readings: Peter Nadin, Richard Prince, Reese Williams, March 29, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Super-8/Berlin: The Architecture of Division, March 30, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Mowry Baden, March 31, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - International Projects: Italy - Doriana Chiarini, April 7, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Three Individual Installations: Ashley Bickerton, Rober Hamon, Justen Ladda, April 7, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - A Decade of New Art: 10th Anniversary Retrospective - Promotional Materials, May 31, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - A Decade of New Art: 10th Anniversary Retrospective - Captions and Publication Texts [1 of 2], May 31, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - A Decade of New Art: 10th Anniversary Retrospective - Captions and Publication Texts [2 of 2], May 31, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - A Decade of New Art: 10th Anniversary Retrospective - Checklists, May 31, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - A Decade of New Art: 10th Anniversary Retrospective - Coordination, Correspondence, May 31, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - A Decade of New Art: 10th Anniversary Retrospective - Installation Instructions, May 31, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - A Decade of New Art: 10th Anniversary Retrospective - Loan Forms, May 31, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - A Decade of New Art: 10th Anniversary Retrospective - Photographic Materials [1 of 2], May 31, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - A Decade of New Art: 10th Anniversary Retrospective - Photographic Materials [2 of 2], May 31, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Five Artists: Taka Amano, Nina Kayem, Alan Steele, Paul Stimson, Marybeth Welch, September 29, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Selections from The Artists File: Artists' Statements, Photographic Materials, November 3, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Selections from The Artists File: Coordination and Promotional, November 3, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Forced Sentiment, December 8, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Dark Rooms: Catalogue Photographs & Text, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Dark Rooms: Flyers & Press Release, January 26, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Dark Rooms: Eva Brandl, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Dark Rooms: James Carpenter, January 26, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Dark Rooms: Jon Rubin, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Dark Rooms: Judith Barry, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Dark Rooms: Photographic Materials, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - 3 Exhibitions Sponsored by The Mark Rothko Foundation, March 9, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 3 Exhibitions Sponsored by The Mark Rothko Foundation: Bert Carpenter, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 3 Exhibitions Sponsored by The Mark Rothko Foundation: Charles Harbutt, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 3 Exhibitions Sponsored by The Mark Rothko Foundation: Duane Zaloudek, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Get It In Writing: An Evening of Readings, March 23, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Five Spanish Artists, April 13, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Five Spanish Artists, April 13, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Five Spanish Artists: Damage, April 13, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Five Spanish Artists: Photographic Materials, April 13, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Super 8 Solar Film Program, May 9, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Memory Jam: Retrospective Performance Series - Artist Research, May 16, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Memory Jam: Retrospective Performance Series - Photographs [1 of 2], May 16, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Memory Jam: Retrospective Performance Series - Photographs [2 of 2], May 16, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Memory Jam: Retrospective Performance Series - Promotional Drafts, May 16, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Memory Jam: Retrospective Performance Series - Robin Winters, May 16, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Projects: Administrative and Promotional, May 25, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Projects: Anita David, May 25, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Projects: Audrey Glassman, May 25, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Projects: Jerry Beck [1 of 2], May 25, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Projects: Patricia Thornley, May 25, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Projects: Sherry Markovitz, May 25, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - "Artists from the Studio in a School", July 13, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Annual Selections from the Artists File: Administrative and Promotional, September 21, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Annual Selections from the Artists File: Photographic Materials, September 21, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - The Artists File Marathon Slide Show, September 28, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Film Event: Organized by David James - Los Angeles, October 24, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Film Event: Organized by Julia Lesage - Chicago, October 25, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Film Event: Organized by Linda Dubler - Atlanta, October 26, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Four Artists: An Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture - Margrit Lewczuk, Lizbeth Marano, Dona Nelson, Jenny Snider, November 2, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - What Does She Want: A Video Exhibition Organized by Lyn Blumenthal, November 2, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - MTV "Art Breaks": Preview and Benefit for Artists Space, December 4, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Immanent Madness: A Film Installation by Seth Weinhardt, December 14, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Split/Vision: Photography Exhibition Organized by Robert Mapplethorpe and Laurie Simmons, December 14, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Split/Vision: Photographic Materials, December 14, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - An Environment of Readings by Four Women Writers: Lynne Tillman, Amy Gerstler, Constance De Jong, Lydia Davis, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - "Famous for 30 Seconds: Artists in the Media, A Video Exhibition", January 26, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Six Sculptors: William Harvey, Lisa Hoke, Steven Schiff, Ritsuko Taho, B. Wurtz, Yuriko Yamaguchi, January 25, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Relations: Three Evenings of Readings, Videotapes, and Film, February 27, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Recent Art from Chicago, March 8, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Moderns in Mind: Gerome Kamrowski, Lee Mullican, Gordon Ouslow-Ford - Administrative, Promotional, April 12, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Moderns in Mind: Research [1 of 2], April 12, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Moderns in Mind: Research [2 of 2], April 12, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - "Social Disease" by Tony Labat, "Two Possibilities" by Larry Millers, April 12, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - The Critics Voices: Volume IV - A Performance Featuring Marvin Heiferman, Gary Indiana, Paul McMahon, Jeff Perrone, May 16, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - From Here to Eternity: Administrative and Promotional, May 24, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - From Here to Eternity: Artists Proposals and Loans, May 24, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - From Here to Eternity: Photographic Materials, May 24, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Film Installations: Wyn Geleynse, May 16, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Slide File Open House: The Artists File Marathon Slide Show, June 14, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Artists from the Studio in School, September 2, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Selections from the Artists File: Photographic Materials, September 18, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Selections from the Artists File: Promotional Materials, September 18, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - The Fairy Tale: Politics, Desire, and Everyday Life [Administrative and Promotional], October 30, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - The Fairy Tale: Artists Research, Catalogue Drafts, October 30, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - The Fairy Tale: Photographic Materials, October 30, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Plato's Cave, Rothko's Chapel, Lincoln's Profile: A Performance by Mike Kelley with Sonic Youth - Administrative and Promotional, December 5, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Plato's Cave, Rothko's Chapel, Lincoln's Profile: Photographs, December 5, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Contained Attitudes: Meuser, Alain Sechas, Jan Van Oost, Ton Zwerver, December 11, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Contained Attitudes: Research, December 11, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Contained Attitudes: Video Program Curated by Chris Dercon, December 11, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Dark Rooms: Anne Bray, Kendall Buster, John Knecht, Charles Long, Carolee Schneemann - Administrative and Promotional, February 5, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Dark Rooms: Rejected Submissions, February 5, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Dark Rooms: Travel, February 5, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Hani Rashid: Kursaal For An Evacuee, February 5, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - TV Sandino: Video Exhibition, February 5, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Abstraction in Process: Fontaine Dunn, Robert Hall, Benje La Rico, Stephen Spretnjak, March 26, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Buying In and Selling Out: Dealing with the Forms of Broadcast Television - A Video Exhibition, March 26, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Marcos, the Mountains, and Mao: Films, Videotape, and a Reading on the Philippines, May 15, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Architecture Project: Lynn and Ian Bader Organized by Patricia C. Phillips, May 21, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Calvert Coggeshall and Frederick Hammersley: Paintings, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Heterogeneity and Alienation: A Video Program Organized by Berenice Reynaud, May 21, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Tourist Attractions: Fantasy and Foreigness Readings, June 25, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Artists from the Studio in a School, September 8, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Floating Values: A Video Program Organized by Chris Hill, October 1, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Selections from the Artists File: Administrative and Promotional, October 1, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Selections from the Artists File: Photographic Materials, October 1, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Underexposed: A Film Series Organized by Andy Moses and Keith Sanborn, November 6, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - We The People: Administrative and Promotional, November 12, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - We The People: Artists Contact Lists, November 12, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - We The People: Correspondence and Loan Forms, November 12, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - We The People: Film and Video Program, November 12, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - We The People: Photographic Materials, November 12, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - We The People: Research, November 12, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Exhibition Schedule, Organization Grant Application, 1987 - 1988 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - In The Streets: Protest Films from the 60s and 80s, Organized by Dan Walworth, January 8, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Other Versions (Perversions): Video Program Organized by Dan Walworth, January 14, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Social Spaces: Exhibition Organized by Valerie Smith [1 of 2], January 14, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Social Spaces: Exhibition Organized by Valerie Smith [2 of 2], January 14, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Colliding: Myth, Fantasy, Nightmare - Exhibition Organized by Michael Auping, February 25, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Unacceptable Appetites: Video Program Organized by Micki McGee, February 25, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - The London Project: Architectural Exhibition [1 of 2], April 14, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - The London Project: Architectural Exhibition [2 of 2], April 14, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Too Black, Too Strong!: Video Tapes and Works on Paper, Organized by Reginald Woolery, April 14, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - James Coleman: "See for Oneself", June 2, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Michael Asher and James Coleman: Organized by Valerie Smith - Administrative and Promotional, June 2, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Michael Asher and James Coleman: Catalogue Text, Essays, June 2, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Michael Asher and James Coleman: Photographic Materials, June 2, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Telling Tales: A Video Program Organized by Dan Walworth, June 2, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Artists from a Studio in a School, August 1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - I Miss the Revolution: Bolek Grecyznski with the Battlefields Project, September 29, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Min Joong Art: A New Cultural Movement from Korea - Administrative and Promotional, September 29, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Min Joong Art: Panel "Cultural Politics Between the First and Third Worlds", October 16, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Min Joong Art: Photographic Materials [1 of 2], September 28, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Min Joong Art: Photographic Materials [2 of 2], September 29, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Min Joong Art: Promotional Materials, September 29, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - The AIDS Crisis is Not Over, AIDS Activisim: Media as Direct Action, November 17, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Purvis Young: Me and My Mink, November 17, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Selections from the Artists File: Administrative and Promotional, November 17, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Selections from the Artists File: Photographic Materials, November 17, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Michael Sorkin: Model City, January 19, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - The North of Ireland: A Selection of Videotapes, Organized by Brendan McMenamin, January 19, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Vidas Perdidas/Lost Lives: Border Art Workshop/Taller de Arte Frontera - Administrative and Promotional, January 19, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Vidas Perdidas/Lost Lives: Photographic Materials and Catalogue, January 19, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Vidas Perdidas/Lost Lives: Research [1 of 2], January 19, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Vidas Perdidas/Lost Lives: Research [2 of 2], January 19, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Dark Rooms: Stephen Barry, Luis Nicolau, Julia Scher, H. Shearer, Jana Sterbak, Patricia Thornley - Administrative, Promotional, March 2, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Dark Rooms: Jana Sterbak, March 2, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Dark Rooms: Rejected Submissions, March 2, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Project: "Winter Flush - A Temporary Garden" by Laurie Palmer [1 of 2], March 2, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Project: "Winter Flush - A Temporary Garden" by Laurie Palmer [2 of 2], March 2, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Signs of Fiction: An Exhibition of Videotapes Curated by Sharon Greytak, March 2, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Barbara Steinman: "Of a Place, Solitary of a Sound, Mute", April 13, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Document and a Dream: A Selection of Videotapes Organized by Dan Walworth, April 13, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Murray Reich and Shirley Jaffe [1 of 2], April 13, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Murray Reich and Shirley Jaffe [2 of 2], April 13, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Coming Soon: Two Evenings of Films in Progress Organized by Leslie Thornton and Dan Walworth, May 19, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 5)